pakstyle.pk 2015-11-09

# Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy of PakStyle.pk

This is the Privacy Policy of PakStyle.pk ("PakStyle.pk" or "We" or "Us") and we respects the privacy of your information. This Privacy Policy governs our online information practices and reflects our commitment to protect your privacy. 

Information we Collect and Use

We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order or submit a product review. Upon posting an order at PakStyle.pk we may ask to enter your: first name, last name, e-mail address, phone number, fax number, city and complete address.

The information we collect from you can be used in one of the following ways: 

  * To verify & confirm your order
  * To personalize your shopping experience
  * To improve the functionality of our website
  * To improve the customer and order processing services
  * To send periodic emails about your order processing & delivery
  * To send periodic emails containing our ongoing offers, promotions and coupons
  * Apart from making delivery of your order via shipping carriers, your information will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent

Cookies: We use cookies which are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if your browser allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

Information Security: We have taken some security measures to ensure the safety & security of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.

Your Consent: By using our website, you consent to our privacy policy.

Changes to the Policy: PakStyle.pk may amend this policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes in the way we use your personal information we will notify you by posting a prominent announcement on our pages.

Contacting Us: If you have any questions or concerns regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us using the information below.

pakstyle.pk@gmail.com  
Call # 0336-2226632
